<odoo>
    <!--Template for hotel folio -->
    <template id="report_asset_policy">
        <t t-call="web.html_container">
            <t t-foreach="docs" t-as="o">
                <t t-call="web.external_layout">

                    <div class="page">
                        <div class="row">
                            <div class="col-xs-12">
                                <div style="padding:30px">
                                    <h3 style="text-align:center;">Employee Laptop Policy</h3><br/>
                                    <ol style="text-align: justify;">
                                        <li style="margin-bottom:10px;"> We encourage employees to use their personal laptops for office use. In that case s/he can avail laptop
                                            allowance (not more than 1200 BDT) only if employee assures management/IT, s/he will get a new laptop
                                            after every 36 months of usage. If employees use their personal laptop computers for official purpose,
                                            company will not bear any other maintenance cost (excluding laptop allowance) for any kind of damage. He
                                            has to ensure safety of that device.
                                        </li>
                                        <li style="margin-bottom:10px;"> Executive and above are eligible to apply (through a laptop allocation form which will be provided by HRD)
                                            for official laptop only if that employee’s supervisor / department head recommend HR with a proper
                                            justification of the requirement/necessity. IT department will issue laptops only when CEO finally approves
                                            the recommendation.
                                        </li>
                                        <li style="margin-bottom:10px;"> After allocation of official laptop, no one can avail laptop allowance. Official laptops are parts office
                                            properties so we encourage employees not to take these outside of office. In case of emergency of work,
                                            employee can take that outside of office compound, we will count that as exception, but device safety and
                                            security must be ensured first. S/he should avoid risky locations and encourage visiting at day time. Laptops
                                            should be kept in a padded carrying case or sleeve during transportation.
                                        </li>
                                        <li style="margin-bottom:10px;"> Laptops that are not secured with a cable and left unattended overnight should be kept in a locked drawer
                                            or cabinet.
                                        </li>
                                        <li style="margin-bottom:10px;"> The login password should be changed at least once every quarter, contact IT for tips on secured password.
                                        </li>
                                        <li style="margin-bottom:10px;"> Individuals should not attempt to install personal software or hardware or change the system configuration
                                            including network settings on office laptops/computers without prior consultation with IT Department.
                                        </li>
                                        <li style="margin-bottom:10px;"> Employee will ensure the confidentiality of all company information including:<br/>
                                            7.1. Corporate Plans, Procedures, Policies, Sales Figures, Demos, or Strategies.<br/>
                                            7.2. Computer Files transferred via USB key, CD, or other media.<br/>
                                            7.3. Corporate communication including but not limited to E-mail, Instant Messaging.
                                        </li>
                                        <li style="margin-bottom:10px;"> Employees will not be held responsible for computer problems resulting from regular usages; however, they
                                            will be held personally responsible for any problems caused by their negligence.
                                        </li>
                                        <li style="margin-bottom:10px;"> Official Laptops can be replaced by the company in case of requirements or damages caused by regular
                                            uses. But all damage, loss or theft of the laptop arising out of negligence of the employee with regard to
                                            above policies will be deducted from the employee’s salary, or any other legal action can be taken by
                                            management.
                                        </li>
                                        <li style="margin-bottom:10px;"> Employee will report Loss or Theft of company laptop to IT or management immediately. In the event of
                                            termination or resignation, all company property, including company laptops, must be returned to
                                            employer.
                                        </li>
                                    </ol>
                                </div>
                            </div>
                        </div>


                        <table class="table table-condensed table-bordered">
                            <tr>
                                <th style="width:50%;">Signature of Employee</th>
                                <th style="width:50%;">Countersigned By</th>
                            </tr>
                            <tr style="height:100px;">
                                <td style="width:50%;"></td>
                                <td style="width:50%;"></td>
                            </tr>
                            <tr>
                                <td style="width:50%;">
                                    Name: <span t-field="o.name"/> <br/>
                                    Designation: <span t-field="o.job_id"/> <br/>
                                    Department: <span t-field="o.department_id"/>
                                </td>
                                <td style="width:50%;">
                                    Name: <span t-field="o.admin_name"/> <br/>
                                    Designation: <span t-field="o.admin_designation"/> <br/>
                                    Department: <span t-field="o.admin_department"/>
                                </td>
                            </tr>
                        </table>
                    </div>
                </t>
            </t>
        </t>
    </template>
</odoo>
